questions = {
    'Math': {
        '100': {
            'question': '2 + 3 = _',
            'answers': ['5', '6', '7', '8'],
            'answer': 0,
            'used' : False
        },
        '200': {
            'question': '2 * 5 + 4 = _',
            'answers': ['5', '6', '14', '10'],
            'answer': 2,
            'used' : False
        },
        '300': {
            'question': '2 + 6 * 8 / 2 = _',
            'answers': ['15', '26', '27', '38'],
            'answer': 1,
            'used' : False
        },
        '400': {
            'question': '6 + 8 % 3 = _',
            'answers': ['5', '2', '7', '8'],
            'answer': 3,
            'used' : False
        }
    },
    'Computer Science': {
        '100': {
            'question': 'which one is computer language',
            'answers': ['English', 'Chinese', 'Java', 'Japan'],
            'answer': 2,
            'used': False
        },
        '200': {
            'question': 'Which CS language is for frontend',
            'answers': ['Java', 'JS', 'C++', 'English'],
            'answer': 2,
            'used': False
        },
        '300': {
            'question': 'When was Java invented ',
            'answers': ['1991', '1995', '2020', '1992'],
            'answer': 0,
            'used': False
        },
        '400': {
            'question': 'Which key word is from Java ',
            'answers': ['component', 'class', 'const', 'pointer'],
            'answer': 1,
            'used' :False
        }
    },
    'WORLD WAR I': {
        '100': {
            'question': 'World War I ended in?',
            'answers': ['1925', '1918', '1920', '1915'],
            'answer': 1,
            'used': False
        },
        '200': {
            'question': 'Whose death sparked World War I?',
            'answers': ['Kaiser Wilhelm', 'Archbishop Ussher', 'Queen Victoria', 'Archduke Franz Ferdinand'],
            'answer': 3,
            'used' :False
        },
        '300': {
            'question': 'Which of these nations was neutral in World War I?',
            'answers': ['Germany', 'Norway', 'Italy', 'England'],
            'answer': 1,
            'used': False
        },
        '400': {
            'question': 'Which of these ships was sunk by a German submarine?',
            'answers': ['Arizona', 'Lusitania', 'Titanic', 'Andrea Doria'],
            'answer': 1,
            'used': False
        }
    },
    'SJSU': {
        '100': {
            'question': 'Where is SJSU located',
            'answers': ['Santa Clara', 'San Jose', 'Sunnyvale', 'Los Angles'],
            'answer': 0,
            'used': False
        },
        '200': {
            'question': 'What is the mascot of SJSU?',
            'answers': ['Lion', 'Sheep', 'Spartan', 'Barbarian'],
            'answer': 2,
            'used' :False
        },
        '300': {
            'question': 'What is the Graduation rate of SJSU ___ ?',
            'answers': ['57%', '1%', '100%', '47%'],
            'answer': 0,
            'used': False
        },
        '400': {
            'question': 'Who is president of SJSU?',
            'answers': ['Johnny Depp', 'Susan Martin', 'Tom Holland', 'Lawrence J Fox'],
            'answer': 2,
            'used' :False
        }
    }
}
